<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DASC blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DASC blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>European Energy Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/2020/12/08/european-energy-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/08/european-energy-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>European Energy Usage: Clean Energy vs. Conventional Using data that is available on the Tidy Tuesday website on European Energy, I will investigate the energy usage among European countries with an emphasis on which countries are the best at using renewable energy and clean energy. I will be examining data from the energy_types.csv file from the Tidy Tuesday website. The data consists of 296 observations and 7 variables. The data displays the energy production from each European country from 2016-2018 and breaks it down by how much energy was produced by conventional thermal, nuclear, hydroelectric, pumped hydroelectric, wind, solar, geothermal, and other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/2020/12/03/a-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/03/a-first-post/</guid>
      <description>NFL Attendance For this project, I will be examining the NFL attendance data from the attendance.csv file on the Tidy Tuesday Website. The data consists of 10,846 observations and 8 variables. The dataset shows the the total attendance and weekly attendance for every NFL team dating back to the 2000 NFL season.
Another dataset that I will be using to explore NFL attendence is the standings.csv file from the Tidy Tuesday website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
